Moon's up high,
shining wide.
Counting sheep on my bed.
Who's still awake?
Tossing and turning?
Little lamb,
wool so white.
Why're you hiding from the rest?
Glow in the dark,
come when the sun sets
Ayayayaya
Ayayayayayaya
I ring my bell,
I ring my bell
Meadow grass swaying slow.
Gentle green with hints of gold.
The twilight paints the end of summer
Electric sheep,
do you dream,
of machines in your sleep?
Or do you dream of running far and free
Ayayayaya
Ayayayayayaya
I ring my bell,
I ring my bell
Ayayayaya
Ayayayayayaya
I ring my bell,
I ring my bell
Oh~DAMIDAMIDAMIO~
Sunlight'll tell me where to go
We laugh and run,
all night long
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~
River guides the way we roam
When the night is gone,
journey will carry on
To the secret untold,
to the wonder we hold
Running out the woods we know,
little sheep we tip tap toe
I wandered high and low,
now I don't walk alone
Together on we go
Wuu
Let's find a way out
Moon's up high,
shining wide.
Set my heart upon a quest
I'm by myself,
but far from lonely
Little lamb,
wool so white.
Why're you running on your own?
I'm just like you,
searching for where I belong.
Ayayayaya Ayayayayayaya
Round and around,
around we go~
To the end I'll keep you close
I'll follow you and be your shadow
Round n round,
around we go.
Count the stars,
then off you go
If I catch you,
promise don't hide again~ again~
I ring my bell,
I ring my bell
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~
Sing the song we used to know
We ride the winds,
into the wild
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~
sing so loud the sky will know
We laugh we run,
until the break of dawn
To the secret untold,
to the wonder we hold
Running out the woods we know,
little sheep we tip tap toe
I wandered high and low,
now I don't walk alone
Together on we go
The stars will take me home