制作人 : Sihan
作曲 : Sihan
编曲 : Sihan
作词 : Lyla P./Sihan/Nellie/Fors/SmileL/Nanyan P/Zilan Li
吉他演奏：Ivan Korop/Daniele Fabio/Dimitris Papageorgiou
合声演唱：Aylin Abbasova/核野
合声编写：SmileL
音频编辑: 杨惠琳
混音：Stephen Kaye
母带：Joe LaPorta@SterlingSound
演唱：Aylin Abbasova
Moon's up high, shining wide. 明月光，夜夜亮
Counting sheep on my bed. 让我来看看：有谁睡得不香？
Who's still awake? Tossing and turning? 把月光拉长，盖在你身上
Little lamb, wool so white. 小羊羔，白又绵
Why're you hiding from the rest? 为什么你和它们不一样？
Glow in the dark, come when the sun sets 尾巴亮亮，让我惊喜异常
Ayayayaya Ayayayayayaya 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
I ring my bell, I ring my bell 摇摇铃铛，摇摇铃铛
Meadow grass swaying slow. Gentle green with hints of gold. 青草长，风轻扬
The twilight paints the end of summer 落日涂抹夏日终章
Electric sheep, do you dream, 小羊羔，听我唱：
of machines in your sleep? 你可也曾坠入梦乡？
Or do you dream of running far and free 也在寻找，遥远的彼方
Ayayayaya Ayayayayayaya 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
I ring my bell, I ring my bell 摇摇铃铛，摇摇铃铛
Oh~DAMIDAMIDAMIO~Sunlight'll tell me where to go 哒咪哒咪哒咪哟~跟随日光
We laugh and run, all night long 追逐白昼，让此刻停留
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~ River guides the way we roam 哒咪哒咪哒咪哟~沿着河流
When the night is gone, journey will carry on 夜色消散，明日继续新的旅途
To the secret untold, to the wonder we hold 向着未言之秘，向着奇思妙想
Running out the woods we know, little sheep we tip tap toe 奔出熟悉的森林，像小羊一般踮步起舞
I wandered high and low, now I don't walk alone 四处旅行，直到找到一位朋友
Together on we go 于是我们一同前行
Wuu 呜
Let's find a way out 一同前行
Moon's up high, shining wide. 明月光，夜夜亮
Set my heart upon a quest 我依然在旅途上
I'm by myself, but far from lonely 请别在意，并不孤单彷徨
Little lamb, wool so white. 小羊羔，白又绵
Why're you running on your own? 其实我和你也一样
I'm just like you, searching for where I belong. 漂泊的孩子想回到梦乡
Ayayayaya Ayayayayayaya 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀 啊呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
Wuu 呜
Round and around, around we go~ 转呀转呀，一路向前；
To the end I'll keep you close 伴你身边，直至终点
I'll follow you and be your shadow 我像影子一样追随你
Round n round, around we go. 转呀转呀，一路向前；
Count the stars, then off you go 数着星星，你便不见
If I catch you, promise don't hide again~ again~ 如果我抓住你了，请答应我：不要再藏起来了
I ring my bell, I ring my bell 摇摇铃铛，摇摇铃铛
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~ Sing the song we used to know 哒咪哒咪哒咪哟~唱起我们熟悉的歌
We ride the winds, into the wild 乘风而行，奔向旷野
DAMIDAMIDAMIO~ sing so loud the sky will know 哒咪哒咪哒咪哟~只要高声歌唱，天空也能听到
We laugh we run, until the break of dawn 夜色消散，明日继续新的旅途
To the secret untold, to the wonder we hold 向着未言之秘，向着奇思妙想
Running out the woods we know, little sheep we tip tap toe 奔出熟悉的森林，像小羊一般踮步起舞
I wandered high and low, now I don't walk alone 四处旅行，直到找到一位朋友
Together on we go 于是我们一同前行
The stars will take me home 星辰终将引我归家